Guide to the Franklin Bowditch Dexter Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Files on Alumni, Circa 1701-1912; Series I; 9' (22 boxes)
  - Beardsley, Horace. 1787 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beardsley, Lucius Nichols. 1888m
  - Beardsley, Miles. 1857 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beardsley, Nehemiah Beach. 1805 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beardsley, Nelson. 1827 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beardsley, Samuel Birdseye. 1815 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beardsley, Sheldon. 1828 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beckwith, Baruch. 1773 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beckwith, Ebenezer White. 1847 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beckwith, George. 1728 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beckwith, George. 1766 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beebe, Lewis. 1771 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Beecher, Lyman. 1797 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    See also: Tyler, Bennett, box 17, folder 207.
  - Beers, Charles Roderick. 1893l (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Beers, Timothy Phelps. 1808
    See: Wooster, Joseph Lucius, box 19, folder 232.
  - Beers, Timothy Phelps. 1847m (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Behan, Newton Isaac. 1860l (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Belcher, John Southard. 1845 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Belden, David. 1785 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Belden, Joshua. 1825 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Belden, Lemuel Whittlesey. 1821
  - Belden, Stanton. 1833 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Belknap, Ebenezer. 1725 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bell, Artemas. 1837m (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bell, Goodloe Bowman. 1852 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bell, Nelson William. 1883
    See: Silliman, George Bliss, box 16, folder 182.
  - Beman, Henry DeWitt. 1851 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Benedict, Abner. 1769 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Benedict, Amzi. 1814 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Benedict, George. 1849 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Benedict, Henry. 1822 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Benedict, Michael Dunning. 1836m (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Benedict, Noah Bennet. 1833m (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Benjamin, Joseph Ritner. 1864 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bennet, Cornelius. 1726 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bennett, Elmer Ellsworth. 1887p (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bennett, Frederick Norman. 1841m (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bennett, Isaac Stockton Keith. 1810 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bennett, James. 1825h (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bennett, Joseph. 1807 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bennett, Lorenzo Thompson. 1825 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bennett, William Comstock. 1858 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bent, Joseph Appleton. 1865 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bent, Samuel Arthur. 1861 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bentley, Edward Warren. 1850 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Benton, William Austin. 1843 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Berdan, James. 1824 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Berry, Heman. 1793 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Berry, John Macdonough. 1847 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    See also: Wilkins, Gouverneur Morris (1847), box 19, folder 222.
  - Berry, Loren Foster. 1877d (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Betts, Arthur Lewis. 1877p (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Betts, John Adams. 1848m (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bibbins, William Burr. 1845
  - Biddle, Charles Penrose. 1866 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bidwell, Barnabas. 1785
  - Bidwell, Marshall Spring. 1858h (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bigelow, Charles Newton. 1820 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bigelow, Henry. 1802
    See: Webster, Ira, box 18, folder 214.
  - Bill, Charles. 1864p (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Billings, Joseph. 1797 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Billings, Noyes. 1819 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Billings, William. 1765 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Billings, William Williams. 1821
    See: Strong, Edward Augustus, box 17, folder 195.
  - Bingham, Hiram. 1819h (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bingham, Silas Long. 1790 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Binney, Horace. 1828 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bird, John. 1786 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bird, Lorenzo Dow. 1839 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bird, Samuel. 1776 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bishop, Addin Lewis. 1857l (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bishop, Edward Gould. 1863 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bishop, Elijah. 1819 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bispham, John Burke. 1830 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, Champion. 1850 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, Clark. 1806
    See: Bissell, Joseph, box 2, folder 18.
  - Bissell, Edward. 1844 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, Gaylord Giles. 1849m (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, Henry Hiram. 1826m (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, Henry Newton. 1839 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, Hezekiah Woodbridge. 1793
  - Bissell, Jonathan Humphrey. 1819 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, Joseph. 1751 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, Samuel. 1823 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bissell, William Church. 1835 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Blachly, Abraham. 1816m (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Black, Philo Carpenter. 1883 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blackman, Ebenezer. 1817 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blackman, Samuel Curtiss. 1793 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blake, Charles Edward. 1865 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blake, Frank Whitney. 1872 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blake, James Pierrepont. 1862 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blakeman, Phineas. 1837 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blakeslee, Amos Cranmer. 1850m (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blakeslee, Erastus. 1863 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Blanchard, Amos. 1826 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Blanchard, Charles Pinckney. 1865 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Blatchley, Joel Sherland. 1850 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bliss, Enos. 1787 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bliss, Judah Lee. 1822 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bliss, Orville Justus. 1871 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bliss, William Edward. 1867 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bliven, Nathan Taylor. 1844m (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bloom, Harvey Harris. 1863 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Board, Charles Howell. 1871 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Boardman, Daniel. 1781 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Boardman, Frederick William Henry. 1823 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Boardman, John Francis. 1829 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bockee, Jacob. 1809 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bockee, Jacob Smith. 1862 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bodwell, Woodbridge. 1836m (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bogert, Cornelius Robert. 1820 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bogue, Aaron Jordan. 1774 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bogue, Ebenezer. 1748 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bogue, Publius Virgilius. 1787 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Boies, Charles Alfred. 1860 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Boltwood, Lucius. 1883
    See: Torrey, Charles Turner, box 17, folder 203.
  - Bontecou, Daniel. 1757 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bonesteel, Virgil Dryden. 1827 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Booth, Charles Edward. 1864 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Booth, Hervey Minor. 1843 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Booth, Sherman Miller. 1841 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bordwell, Joel. 1756 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Botsford, Amos. 1763
    See: box 20, folder 237.
  - Botsford, William. 1792 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bowe, Daniel. 1859 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bowen, Matthew. 1790 non-graduate (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bowen, William. 1766 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bowers, Benjamin Franklin. 1819m (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bowers, Josiah. 1816m (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bowles, George Whitefield. 1806 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Boyd, John. 1821
  - Boyden, Ebenezer. 1825 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Boyle, John. 1807 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    See also: Whitehead, Amos, box 18, folder 219.
  - Bradford, Jeremiah. 1779 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bradley, Abraham. 1723 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bradley, Alvin Chase. 1831 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bradley, Charles William. 1846h (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bradley, Dan. 1789 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bradley, Henry Roswell. 1853 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bradley, Jesse Smith. 1800 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bradley, Joseph Habersham. 1821
  - Bradley, Levi Barnes. 1849 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bradley, Lewis Bliss. 1833m (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bradley, Philip Burr. 1758
  - Brainard, Dyar Throop. 1810 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Brainerd, David. 1741 non-graduate
    See: Youngs, David, box 19, folder 234.
  - Brainerd, Joseph Hungerford. 1822 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Brainerd, Timothy Green. 1830 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Brandegee, John Jacob. 1843 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brandegee, Marius. 1843 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brandon, Robert Lindsey. 1856 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Breed, Edward Andrews. 1844 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Breed, Henry Lincoln. 1859 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Breed, John McLaren. 1768
    See: Brewer, Daniel, box 3, folder 23.
  - Breed, Shubael. 1778
  - Breed, Simeon. 1781
  - Breed, William James. 1831 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brent, Charles Lewis. 1849 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brent, James Harvey. 1861
    See: Steele, Thomas Clark, box 16, folder 192.
  - Brewer, Daniel. 1765 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brewer, Edwin. 1823 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brewer, Josiah. 1821 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brewster; Cyrus. 1763 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brewster, Cyrus. 1841h (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brickell, James Noaille. 1845 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brigham, Clayton Harcourt. 1888 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brinley, William Henry. 1881m (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brinsmade, Daniel Nathaniel. 1772 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brinsmade, James Beebee. 1845 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brintnall, William. 1721 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brinton, John Ferree. 1848 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Briscoe, Joseph Rowland. 1843m (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bristol, Albert Gallatin. 1827 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bristol, Moses. 1813 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bristol, Simeon Charles. 1840 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brockway, John Hall. 1820 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bromley, Isaac Hill. 1853 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bronson, Thomas. 1829 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brooks, Daniel. 1839 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brooks, David. 1768 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brooks, Joshua Twing. 1863h (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brooks, Levi. 1815 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brooks, Thomas. 1755 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brown, Daniel. 1783
  - Brown, Daniel Bishop. 1800 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, David Beveridge. 1868l (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Ebenezer. 1813 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    See also: Welles, Elijah Gardiner, box 18, folder 215.
  - Brown, Frederick Anson. 1824 non-graduate (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Garrett Garnsey. 1809 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Henry Clinton. 1826m (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Horace Atwell. 1863l (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, James. 1747 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, John. 1771 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Leonard Treat. 1867 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Samuel. 1749 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Samuel Watson. 1850 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Solymon. 1812 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Waldo. 1821 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brown, William. 1784
  - Browning, Albert Gordon. 1863m (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brownson, David. 1762 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Brownson, Nathan. 1761 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Brundage, Abner. 1826h (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Brush, David. 1804 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Brush, Perlee. 1793 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Brush, Samuel Scudder. 1795 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bruyn, Johannes. 1840 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bryan, Elijah Fowler. 1829m (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bryant, William. 1747
  - Buck, David. 1823 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Buck, Edward. 1835 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Buckingham, Daniel. 1735
    See: Buckingham, Samuel Giles, box 3, folder 26.
    See: Wakeman, Stephen, box 18, folder 211.
  - Buckingham, Gideon. 1765 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    See also: Buckingham, Samuel Giles, box 3, folder 26.
  - Buckingham, Jedidiah. 1714 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Buckingham, Joseph. 1723
  - Buckingham, Samuel Giles. 1833 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Buckingham, Stephen. 1702h (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Buckland, Joseph Payson. 1857 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Budlong, James. 1851 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Buehler, George Wolf. 1856 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Buel, Frederick. 1836 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Buell, Richard Miles. 1852m (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Buffet, William Lewis. 1819 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Buffet, William Platt. 1812 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Buford, Charles. 1818 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bugbee, Francis. 1818 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bulkeley, Charles Edwin. 1856 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bulkley, Chauncey. 1817
  - Bulkley, Henry Daggett. 1821
  - Bulkley, Lucius Duncan. 1866
    See: Daggett, Henry, box 5, folder 49.
  - Bulkley, Moses. 1873 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bulkley, Peter. 1785 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bulkley, Tuzar. 1865 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bull, Edward. 1816 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bull, George. 1828 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bull, John Catlin. 1849 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bull, Nehemiah. 1723 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bullard, Royal. 1810 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bunker, James Madison. 1832 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bunn, Charles Wesley. 1853 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bunnell, James Fitch. 1826 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burch, John. 1809 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burch, John Christopher. 1847 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burden, Thomas Legaré. 1830 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burgess, Anson. 1818 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burleigh, Rinaldo. 1803 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burnham, Jedidiah Kent. 1854 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burnham, Sherburne Wesley. 1878h (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burnham, Zebulon Perkins. 1818m (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Burr, Aaron. 1735 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Burr, David Judson. 1839 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    See also: Denison, Henry Waldo, box 6, folder 51.
  - Burr, Hudson. 1853 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Burr, Isaac. 1717 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Burr, Samuel Jones. 1859h (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Burrall, Jonathan. 1781
    See: Davies, Thomas, box 5, folder 49.
  - Burrall, Thomas Davies. 1803 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Burrall, William. 1771 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Burritt, Henry Lewellen Wakeman. 1844m (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bush, George Marland. 1881m (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bush, James Clark. 1871p
    See: Clark, John, box 4, folder 38.
  - Bush, James Smith. 1844 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bush, Katherine Jeannette. 1901p
  - Bush, Ralph Isaacs. 1802 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Butler, Amos. 1767 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Butler, Frederick. 1785 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    See also: Williams, Timothy, box 19, folder 225.
  - Butler, Norman William Henderson. 1830 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Buttles, Albert Barnes. 1842 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Butts, Asa. 1822
  - Caldwell, Henry. 1784 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    See also: Brown, William, box 20, folder 237.
  - Caldwell, Jacob. 1729 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Caldwell, Nathaniel. 1757 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Caldwell, Walter Lord. 1892p (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Camp, Albert Barlow. 1822 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Camp, Henry Bates. 1831 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Camp, Ichabod. 1743
    See: box 20, folder 238.
  - Camp, Joseph Eleazar. 1787 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Camp, Samuel. 1764 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Campbell, Amasa Brainard. 1833 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Campbell, James Alexander. 1882 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Cande, John. 1774 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Candee, Joel Gillett. 1825m (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Candee, Judson. 1846m (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Canfield, Henry Judson. 1806 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Canfield, Orlando. 1818 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Canning, Edward Weeks Boldero. 1852h (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Carlton, Henry. 1806 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Carpenter, Nelson. 1824m (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carpenter, Robert John. 1859 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carpenter, Zachary Taylor. 1870 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carr, Wilson Cary Nicholas. 1846
  - Carrier, Oscar Mortimer. 1860 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carrington, Edward. 1823 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carrington, James Hopkins. 1875 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carrington, Samuel. 1786 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carruth, James Harrison. 1832 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carter, Edwin Osgood. 1837 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Carter, Josiah Mason. 1836 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Cary, Lorenzo. 1838 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Cary, Samuel. 1755
    See: Devotion, Samuel Huntington, box 6, folder 52.
  - Case, Francis Hiram. 1822 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Case, Seth Ely. 1847 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Case, William. 1821 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Casey, Edward William. 1828 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Casto, William Thomas. 1845 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Arnold Welles. 1862 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Benjamin Spencer. 1859 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Charles Taylor. 1786 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Charles Taylor. 1822 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Charles Taylor. 1856 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Elbert Howard. 1896p (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Hasket Derby. 1859 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, John. 1839 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, John Mortimer. 1820 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Lynde. 1786 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Lynde Alexander. 1853 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Reginald Woodward. 1908 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Russell. 1784 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, Samuel Hall. 1849m (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Catlin, William Conant. 1840m (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Chadbourne, Albert Hiram. 1872l (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chaffee, Hezekiah Bradley. 1809 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chaffee, Samuel Griswold. 1810 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chalker, Isaac. 1728 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chamberlain, Robert Linton. 1861 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chamberlain, Theophilus. 1765 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chamberlain, William Young. 1836m (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, George. 1813m (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, John. 1759 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, John. 1772 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, John. 1808 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, Joseph. 1842 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, Joshua. 1747 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, Rufus. 1806 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, Thomas Bradbury. 1745 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, William. 1773 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, William George. 1849 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chandler, William Henry. 1839 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Channing, Henry William. 1807 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chanute, Joseph Arthur. 1880p (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chapin, Augustus Lyman. 1817 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapin, Calvin. 1788 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapin, Henry Dwight. 1814 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapin, Nathan Colton. 1844 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chaplin, Ebenezer. 1763 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, Daniel. 1707 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    See also:Wakeman, Stephen, box 18, folder 211.
  - Chapman, Daniel. 1789 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, Daniel Chase. 1866 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, Ezekiel Jones. 1799 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, Henry. 1805 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, Hezekiah. 1766 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, John Henry. 1876p (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, Robert Hett. 1850 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, Timothy Pitkin. 1868 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chapman, Zachariah. 1763 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Chase, Alexander Ralston. 1829m (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chase, George. 1817 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chase, Harvey. 1800 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chatfield, John. 1735 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chaulkins, John. 1788
  - Chauncey, Ichabod Wolcott. 1723 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chauncey, Nathaniel. 1702 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chedsey, Nathan Augustus. 1848l
  - Cheney, Abiel. 1771 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chesebrough, Henry Augustus. 1820 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chesebrough, Peleg. 1755 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chesebrough, Robert John. 1817 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chester, Edward. 1848h (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chester, George Foot. 1846 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chester, Orlando. 1831 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chester, Stephen Mitchell. 1813 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Chiffelle, Thomas Philotheus. 1803 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Child, Jeremiah. 1757 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Child, Linus. 1824 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Child, Willard. 1817 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Chittendon, William Henry. 1883m (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Christman, Joseph Alonzo. 1857 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Church, Aaron. 1765 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Church, Austin. 1823m (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Church, Frederick Nathaniel. 1857 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Church, John Barker. 1829 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Churchill, Silas. 1787 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clack, Franklin Hulse. 1847l (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clap, Caleb. 1785 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clap, Ezra. 1740 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clapp, Alexander Huntington. 1842
    See: Stone, Charles Stewart, box 16, folder 194.
  - Clark, Charles Washburn. 1875 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clark, Elijah. 1801 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clark, Elijah Wells. 1839m (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clark, Gamaliel. 1734
  - Clark, Gerardus. 1804 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Jehu. 1794 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Jesse. 1756 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, John. 1806 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, John Peyton. 1848 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Joseph Edgar. 1845m (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Joseph Washburn. 1837m (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Perkins Kirkland. 1838 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Smith. 1817 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Thomas March. 1831 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, William Bardwell. 1861 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, William Taylor. 1843m (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Wilson Hart. 1845l (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clarke, Abraham Lynsen. 1785 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Addison Lewis. 1858 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Charles Ezra. 1809 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Edwards. 1815 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Elbert Willett. 1867 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, John. 1840h (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, John Proctor. 1878 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Jonathan Tillotson. 1854 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Peter Gilchrist. 1821h (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Richard. 1762
    See: box 20, folder 239.
  - Clarke, Robert. 1830 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Tertius Strong. 1824 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clarke, Thomas Slidell. 1875 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1811
    See: Perot, Edward, box 14, folder 155.
  - Class of 1815
    See: Youle, Joseph, box 19, folder 234.
  - Clayton, John Middleton. 1815
  - Cleaveland, Ebenezer. 1748 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Cleaveland, Jocelyn Plant. 1876l (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clemens, Jermiah William. 1873 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Clement, Peabody. 1774 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Clemson, William Frederick. 1829 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Clendenin, James Henry. 1872 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Cleveland, Henry Augustus. 1870 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Cleveland, Richard Falley. 1824 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Cleveland, William Henry. 1823m (Box 4, Folder 40)
    See also: Bacon, Asa, box 1, folder 6.
  - Close, David. 1771 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Close, Odle. 1842 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Close, Reuben Holmes. 1826 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Cloud, John Wurts. 1823 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Coates, Alfred Washington. 1843m (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Coates, Elias Frank. 1843m (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Coburn, John Buchanan. 1838 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cochran, Charles William. 1875 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cochran, Robert. 1846 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Codman, William. 1815 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Coe, Truman. 1825h (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Coe, Wesley Roswell. 1892p
  - Coffing, Churchill. 1834 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cogswell, Mason Fitch. 1829 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cogswell, Samuel. 1777 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cogswell, William Henry. 1823m (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cohen, George Eugene. 1884 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cott, Alfred. 1856 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Colt, Benjamin Billings. 1822 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Coit, Daniel Lathrop. 1864 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cott, Gurdon Saltonstall. 1828 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cott, John Calkins. 1818 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Colt, Thomas Winthrop. 1821 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Colt, William. 1761 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cole, Erastus. 1834h (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Cole, Mathew. 1783 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Cole, Samuel. 1731 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Coleman, Henry. 1874m (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Coleman, James Beakes. 1829m (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Coleman, Lyman. 1817 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Coleman, Robert. 1842 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Coles, Oliver. 1823 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Collins, Aaron Cooke. 1786 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Collins, Josiah. 1826 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Collins, Levi. 1802
  - Collis, John Tucker. 1820 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Colt, Peter. 1764 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Colton, Benjamin. 1710
  - Colton, Calvin. 1812 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Colton, David Burton. 1841 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Colton, George. 1756 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Colton, George. 1804 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Colton, Horace Benjamin. 1850h
    See: Welles, Martin, box 18, folder 215.
  - Colton, Melancthon Howe. 1829 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Colton, Simeon. 1806 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Comstock, David Close. 1830 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Comstock Eleutheros Dana. 1807 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Conant, Eleazar. 1776 (Box 5, Folder 43)